(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-09-30T01:21:36.162334",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
恋
[Song: "Koi" (Love)]
営みの 街暮れたら
When dusk falls on the bustling city,
色めき 風たちは運ぶわ
playful winds blow into life,
カラスと 人々の群れ
carrying crows and crowds of people.
意味なんかないさ
Life doesn't need a grand meaning,
暮らしがあるだけ
it just goes on.
ただ腹を空かせて
Simply working up an appetite,
君の元へ帰るんだ
I'll head home back to you.
物心ついたらふと
Ever since I became aware of the world,
見上げて思うことが
I've looked up and realized
この世にいる誰もが
that every single person in this world
二人から
originated from a pair of two.
胸の中にあるもの
What lies deep inside your heart,
いつか見えなくなるもの
what will one day vanish from sight,
それはそばにいること
is the simple act of being by your side.
いつも思い出して
Always remember that.
君の中にあるもの
What lies inside of you,
距離の中にあること
what exists across the distance between us...
恋をしたのはあなたの
Falling in love was all because of you—
指の混ざり 頬の香り
our entwined fingers, the scent of your cheek.
夫婦を超えてゆけ
Let's go beyond just being a married couple.
みにくいと 秘めた思いは
Feelings kept hidden away, thought to be ugly,
色づき 白鳥は運ぶわ
turn colorful as swans carry them away,
当たり前を変えながら
changing what we take for granted as they go.
恋節 泣き出せない
Unspoken romantic melodies, unable to cry out,
成り高を思う強がりにも
even in bluffing to look bigger than we are...
愛が生まれるのは
Love is something that always begins
一人から
from just one person.
胸の中にあるもの
What lies deep inside your heart,
いつか見えなくなるもの
what will one day vanish from sight,
それはそばにいること
is the simple act of being by your side.
いつも思い出して
Always remember that.
君の中にあるもの
What lies inside of you,
距離の中にあること
what exists across the distance between us...
恋をしたのはあなたの
Falling in love was all because of you—
指の混ざり 頬の香り
our entwined fingers, the scent of your cheek.
夫婦を超えてゆけ
Let's go beyond just being a married couple.
泣き顔も
Even your tearful face,
黙る夜も
even the quiet, silent nights,
揺れる笑顔も
even your swaying smile,
いつまでも
forever and ever,
forever and ever.
胸の中にあるもの
What lies deep inside your heart,
いつか見えなくなるもの
what will one day vanish from sight,
それはそばにいること
is the simple act of being by your side.
いつも思い出して
Always remember that.
君の中にあるもの
What lies inside of you,
距離の中にあること
what exists across the distance between us...
恋をしたのはあなたの
Falling in love was all because of you—
指の混ざり 頬の香り
our entwined fingers, the scent of your cheek.
夫婦を超えてゆけ
Let's go beyond just being a married couple.
二人を超えてゆけ
Let's go beyond just two people.
一人を超えてゆけ
Let's transcend being alone.
恋
[Title: Love]
みなさん！
Everyone!
みなさん、みなさん、みなさん！ ヘイヘイ！
Everyone, everyone, everyone! Hey, hey!
What's up, everybody?
Welcome!
So out of order.
Yes! Welcome, welcome, welcome!
Welcome! Yay!
自己紹介、自己紹介！ Introduction!
Self-introductions, self-introductions! Introductions!
I guess I get to go, senpai of us all!
Eh? Yeah.
Huh? Yeah.
Really? Does that really count?
Senpai by like, what, an hour? Half an hour or so?
All righty, fine!
So be it! みなさん, it is I, Mori Calliope of HoloMyth! What's up, everybody?
So be it! Everyone, it is I, Mori Calliope of HoloMyth! What's up, everybody?
I do a lot of things, and I've been here a while.
Four is my favorite number, but six is good too! Michael, come here.
Come here, come here, come here!
Anyway, よろしく! And who's next? Who's next?
Anyway, nice to meet you! And who's next? Who's next?
Kikkeriki! I am Takanashi Kiara from Hololive Myth!
How's it going? It's six years...
...and I am surrounded by Myth, Myth, Myth, Myth, Myth, Myth...
That's my introduction. I still don't have anything in particular after six years!
Now, what about you? Do you have a special introduction?
Yes she does, I'm ready for it.
Wah! Wah! Wah!
Good morning, afternoon, evening, everyone!
Ninomae Ina'nis of Hololive Myth!
On this wonderful day!
She was shaking her legs earlier! She was scared!
I was not!
大丈夫だよ... よしよし...
It's okay... There, there...
It's gonna be okay.
Don't dance too hard, you know? If you dance too hard, you'll get soft!
Okay, everybody! Congratulations on six years!
Shake hands, shake hands!
And check it out! After all this time, we also have...
We've all done live shows!
Check out the solo outfits! We have solo outfits!
So much has happened in these six years, huh?
Done a lot, huh?
I mean, I feel like six years ago, we never would have even thought that we could do that, you know?
Do you guys still remember the very first time we met each other on Discord?
Yeah, it was weird! It was weird.
The introduction channel, where like everybody typed like a paragraph about themselves?
Yeah, and you didn't mention drawing at all, so we were all so surprised!
She was hiding it even from us!
Well, that made it even more impressive!
So this stream is supposed to celebrate our six years together.
Six!
And we have a hashtag for that, too, right here!
#Myth6Years!
Use it a lot on Twitter, etc.!
Capture your favorite moments and share them with us, because we look at that stuff, you know!
We love it! We love...
We got six years of dancing, so...
And we want you guys to take pictures of them, okay?
Beautiful pictures because not only are we wearing our beautiful outfits, but we also have this beautiful stage, right?
Yeah! High up in the sky, and...
...and I get a feeling that the seasons will change!
Depending upon the songs that we sing.
That's probably true.
And we already showed them a little bit...
...of the seasons with the first song that we performed,
「恋」！
"Koi"!
I like that we're doing this one, because we did the song cover for it, too!
We did! And it was really good!
I really like how it turned out. There were all these cute scenes with us like cooking together and hanging out.
It was cool! Such a cute song.
No, no, I don't want that.
I'm not into lollipops. You have your own lollipop, you already licked it, I don't want it.
Fighting down to... ガキ、ガキ！
Fighting down to... Brats, brats!
We gotta perform, we can't eat too much candy!
Yeah, fine, I'll move past it all.
So that's the sassy lost child that we have here, huh?
She's so small! You need to calm down.
Can we just say that in our solo live outfits, she has never been this small in comparison before?
How tiny are you? They nerfed my height!
That's so tiny! Are you really this tiny?
Like our gaki cousin, little cousin or something like that.
Like our bratty cousin, little cousin or something like that.
Are we her aunties, or her mommies, or her sisters?
Can we go to...
やめろー！
Stop it!
Can we go to PE after this?
No, no, no, we can't. We have that at home.
But Ina-chan, you know what?
At the end of this stream, we'll have a surprise for you and everybody else!
And you won't want to miss it, so make sure that you behave for the entire live.
No, stay until the end, Ina! And stay until the end, everybody in there, too! Okay?
We're safe this time, Calliope.
Let's go!
All right, shall we?
行こうぞ！
Here we go!
Let's do this!
Next song!
September
辛子色のシャツ 追いながら
Chasing after your mustard-yellow shirt,
飛び乗った電車のドア
I jumped through the train doors.
いけないと知りながら
Even though I knew I shouldn't,
振り向けば隠れた
when you turned around, I hid.
街には色づいたクレヨンが
The town's colorful crayons
涙目で染めて走る
run blurred through my tearful eyes.
年上の人に会う
Knowing you had a date
約束と知ってて
to meet an older woman...
September そしてあなたは
September, and then you,
September 秋に変わった
September, changed like autumn.
夏の日差しが弱まるように
Just as the summer sunlight weakens,
心に影がさした
a shadow fell over my heart.
September そして九月は
September, and September is
September さよならの国
September, the land of goodbyes.
ほどきかけてる愛の結び目
The knot of love coming undone,
涙が木ノ葉になる
my tears turn into falling leaves.
会ってその人に頼みたい
I want to meet her and ask her,
彼のこと返してねと
"Please give him back to me."
でもダメね 気の弱さ
But I can't, my weak heart...
唇も震える
Even my lips are trembling.
September そしてあなたは
September, and then you,
September 秋に変わった
September, changed like autumn.
話すことさえなくなるなんて
To think we'd have nothing left to talk about
私に飽きた証拠
is proof you got tired of me.
September そして九月は
September, and September is
September さよならの国
September, the land of goodbyes.
巡る季節の彩りの中
Amid the colors of turning seasons,
一番寂しい月
it's the most lonely month.
借りていた辞書になり
In the dictionary I borrowed,
明日返すわ
which I'll return tomorrow...
「ラブ」という言葉だけ
I cut out only the word "love,"
切り抜いたあと それが Goodbye
and after that, it's Goodbye.
September そしてあなたは
September, and then you,
September 秋に変わった
September, changed like autumn.
私一人が傷つくことが
Me being the only one getting hurt
残された優しさね
is the last kindness left.
September そして九月は
September, and September is
September さよならの国
September, the land of goodbyes.
トリコロールの海辺の服も
Even those tricolor seaside clothes,
二度と着ることはない
I'll never wear them again.
September
気付けば靴は汚れ 錆びついた両刃つたう雨
Before I realized it, my shoes were dirty, and rain trickled down the rusted double-edged blade.
憧れはそのままで 夢から目覚めた先には夢
My longing remains unchanged, and waking from a dream leads only to another dream.
聞こえたその泣き声 消える手前のむせび散る哀れ
I heard that cry, a choking sorrow scattering just before it fades away.
憧れのその先へ うずくまる君を見つけるため
Beyond that longing, to find you cowering there.
行け 行け 追いつけない速度で
Go, go, at an unreachable speed,
飛べ インパルス加速して
Fly, accelerated by impulse,
行け 居処を感じるために生まれてきたんだ
Go! I was born to feel where I belong.
未来を掴んで 期待値を越えて 額に刺さる風
Seize the future, surpass expectations, with the wind piercing your forehead.
今に見よ きっと君の眩しさに誰もが気づくだろう
Just wait and see, surely everyone will notice your brilliance soon.
相応しい声で 視線追い越して 虚空を越えて行け
With a fitting voice, overtaking every gaze, cross through the void and go.
見違えていく君の指から今 手を放す
From your transforming fingers, I now let go of your hand.
気付けば謎は解かれ 宿命ごと見慣れた板の上
Before I realized it, the mystery was solved, along with fate, upon these familiar boards.
あの頃焦がれたような 大人になれたかな
Have I become the adult I yearned to be back then?
そう君の群青は 君が自分で選んだ旅だ
Yes, your deep blue is a journey you chose for yourself,
そして掴んだのなら 誰も彼もすべて君のものだ
And if you've seized it, then everything and everyone belongs to you.
僕の夢になって 弓を番えて 狙いを定めて
Becoming my dream, nock the arrow to the bow, take aim,
強く引いた 今君は決して風になれない
And pull back hard; right now you can never become the wind.
矢になって 行け
Become the arrow and go!
飛べ 決して振り向かないで
Fly! Never look back!
飛べ もう届かない場所へ
Fly to a place beyond reach!
行け 行け 行け 君はいつだって輝いていた
Go, go, go, you were always shining!
未来を掴んで 期待値を越えて 額に刺さる風
Seize the future, surpass expectations, with the wind piercing your forehead.
今に見よ きっと君の眩しさに誰もが気づくだろう
Just wait and see, surely everyone will notice your brilliance soon.
相応しい声で 視線追い越して 虚空を越えて行け
With a fitting voice, overtaking every gaze, cross through the void and go.
見違えていく君の指から今 手を放す
From your transforming fingers, I now let go of your hand.
はじめてのキッスは 涙の味がした
My first kiss tasted like tears,
まるでドラマみたいな恋 見つからなかったように 灰色のベルが鳴る
Like a romance out of a drama, as if never found, the grey bell tolls...
冷たい冬の風が 頬をかすめる
The cold winter wind grazes my cheek,
吐いた白息で 両手を擦った
I rubbed my hands together with my white exhaled breath.
街はイルミネーション 魔法をかけたみたい
The city is lit with illuminations, as if under a magic spell,
裸の街灯がキラキラ
Bare streetlights shine brightly.
悲しくても
Even though it was sad,
嫌だった この気持ち抑えてきた
I hated it, suppressing these feelings...
前から決めていた事だから これでいいの
Because it's something I decided long ago, this is for the best,
ふたりはもう...
The two of us are no longer...
知らない
Strangers.
ありがとう さようなら 切ない片想い
Thank you, goodbye, my painful one-sided love.
足をとめたら 思い出してしまう
If I stop in my tracks, I'll end up remembering.
だから ありがとう さようなら 泣いたりしないから
So thank you, goodbye, I won't cry anymore.
そう思った 途端にふわり
Just as I thought that, gently...
舞い降りてくる雪 触れたら溶けて消えた
The fluttering snow melted and vanished the moment I touched it.
粉雪続く大通り
On the main street where powder snow falls,
寄り添ってる二人 楽しそう
a couple walks side-by-side, looking so happy.
「ほら見て 初雪！」
"Look, the first snow!"
君とあんな風になりたくて
Wanting to be like that with you,
初めて作った
for the first time I knitted
手編みのマフラー
a handmade scarf.
どうしたら渡せたんだろう
How could I have given it to you?
意気地なし
I was such a coward,
怖かっただけ
just so scared.
思い出になるなら
If this is just going to become a memory,
このままで構わないって
keeping things as they are would be fine, I said,
それはほんとなの？
but is that really true?
ありがとう サヨナラ
Thank you, goodbye.
いつかこんな時が来てしまうこと
That a time like this would come eventually...
なのに
...and yet...
ありがとう サヨナラ
Thank you, goodbye.
体が震えてる
My body is trembling.
もうすぐ列車が来るのに
Even though the train is coming soon.
それは今になって 私を苦しめる
Only now does it hurt me so much.
繋がりたい
I want us to be connected.
どれほど願っただろう
How much did I wish for it?
この手は
These hands...
空を切る
...reach out into empty air.
ねぇ サヨナラって
Hey, saying goodbye...
痛い
...hurts so much.
行かなくちゃ
I have to go,
そんなの分かってる
I know that.
君が優しいことも知ってる
I also know how kind you are.
だから この手を離してよ
So please, let go of my hand.
出会えてよかった
I'm glad I met you.
君が好き
I love you.
ありがとう サヨナラ
Thank you, goodbye.
一言が言えない
I can't say those simple words.
今だけでいい 私に勇気を
Just for now, give me courage.
「解けて」
"Melt away,"
かじかんだ手 君との距離はゼロ
my frozen hand... The distance between us is zero.
今だけは泣いていいよね
It's okay to cry just for now, right?
もう言葉はいらない
No more words are needed.
お願い ギュッとしてて
Please, just hold me tight.
来年の今頃には
By this time next year,
どんな私がい(て)
what kind of person will I be,
どんな君がいるのかな
and what kind of person will you be?
Wow, you got some extensions!
Extensions? I don't remember getting anything like that.
Your hair is even longer!
Heh, it's fashionable, though, don't you think?
It looks kind of familiar.
Hm... Like maybe we're missing something... Oh!
Oh, you have another arm, too?
Whoa, there. Hold on a second, something's...
You're growing, huh?
Not only has the season changed...
I lost count!
Wait, it looks like we've lost somebody... Welcome back!
Hi! Hello!
You're here, you're here! Ina, nice hair!
Oh, thank you.
The seasons have changed.
Yes, it's getting a little warmer, thank goodness.
It was kind of cool, you know? It was a little chilly...
Spring! Yay! So beautiful!
Yeah, check it out. The stage is so pink!
I actually really like the color pink now after these six years.
Character development! That's good, that's good.
And we're wearing yukata, kimono, whatever you want it to be!
And we all went for kind of a blue color, yeah?
Yeah, we do look like we're about to drop a sweet enka album.
Isn't this how they pose?
どっこいしょ、どっこいしょ！ どっこいしょ、どっこいしょ！
Dokkoisho, dokkoisho! Dokkoisho, dokkoisho!
ソーラン、ソーラン！ ソーラン、ソーラン！ ヤーレン、ソーラン！
Soran, soran! Soran, soran! Yaren, soran!
Okay, that's not what we're doing! We're not releasing that!
So we did a bunch of songs...
Like, for example?
For example, "Step and Step"... That's not that one!
That you sang! No, please!
But this is a really iconic old Japanese song, okay?
It was so cute. I hope you guys enjoyed this cover too.
Yeah. Right?
Yeah, Ina, did you know it before?
No.
No? Calli, did you know it before?
No. First time hearing it?
I think everyone in the chat will also, when they hear the word September...
I think everyone in the chat, when they hear the word "September"...
No, no, no! That's a different song!
No, this is how we change the impression of September!
When we say September, you don't think of that September, you think about this September with me and Ina, okay?
Yeah, it's just for now.
Yeah! What else did we perform?
Oh, I also saw you did some ballet skating moves.
Are you a filthy archer? I'm disgusted.
You hate archers? I hate archers.
But Genshin... They're such cheaters!
I've never seen this anime, but is there actually an archer in there?
Yeah. Wait, really? No.
Oh, no! There are skaters, though.
Oh! Figure skaters. That's not a skate!
Oh, I can! I can do it. I'm all right.
I can skate too. Okay! Really? We should go, we should go!
I can ice skate! That was my favorite hobby when I was younger.
It's a promise.
Anyway, I loved your low tones. - Yes, thank you. - It was really hot.
No, no, no, it came out beautifully. You sounded wonderful.
Thank you! And I got to sing with Kiara as the snow fell.
We talked and sang a song about first love... - It was super cute.
Weren't we so cute? - It's just what happens when first love ends...
Takamori! So, it feels wholesome to me, I don't know.
君に決めて... Mwa, mwa, no kissu! Mwa, mwa, mwa! Kissu.
I choose you... Mwa, mwa, kisses! Mwa, mwa, mwa! Kisses.
How did that make you feel, everybody in the chat?
Were you jealous, or were you happy for us?
Think carefully about your answer.
Were you happy for us? - Totally, okay. Thank you.
They're definitely saying yes. - Yay!
Well, we have also changed costume. - Yes.
Blue! We're so blue!
White and pink. White, blue, pink... Red, white, and...
Red, white, and blue!
Not quite. Goldfish, Kingyo, and... Mizu-iro.
Not quite. Goldfish, Kingyo, and... light blue.
'Cause I got purple purps.
あー、そうだね。
Ah, that's right.
Wait, is this morning glory?
Ah, I thought they were jellyfish. - Are they jellyfish?
No, I think it's morning... morning glory!
It could also be Austrian bread! That's exactly the shape of Austrian bread!
Do the breads come in those colors?
No! Well, maybe if they're moldy!
Ara ara! Hope you never eat one of those! Don't eat moldy bread!
Have you eaten moldy bread before, everybody? No? Are you sure?
Stale, stale bread. Why is this what we're talking about during our concert?
It's okay. A little whimsy is fine.
But now how about we get serious for a moment and sing a song... a曲, song.
But now how about we get serious for a moment and sing a song... a song, song.
Shut up! Stop it!
Let's sing a song that's a little bit emoi. I was listening to the lyrics and practicing it...
Let's sing a song that's a little bit emotional. I was listening to the lyrics and practicing it...
...and I was like, "Hmm, you know, there are a couple lyrics here and there..."
"...that remind me of the struggles that we have gone through, and how I want to go forward with you guys."
So it made me kind of like, "Ah, emoi." So I hope we can sing it well together.
So it made me kind of like, "Ah, emotional." So I hope we can sing it well together.
We will! We will! And let's do it in these slightly restrictive...
But they're really stretchy! Okay! All right, enough of that!
You like that. Don't do that.
Positions! Now we start. Now we dance and sing.
All right, listen to our next song: "Suzume".
君の中にある 赤と青き線
The red and blue lines inside of you,
それらが結ばれるのは 心の臓
the place where they are bound is the heart.
風の中でも 負けないような声で
With a voice that won't lose even to the wind,
届ける言葉を 今は育ててる
I am now nurturing the words to deliver to you.
時はまくらぎ 風はにかはだ
Time is a sleeper, the wind is bare skin,
...うぶすな
...guardian deity,
人はかげろう
human life is a fleeting mirage.
「なんで泣いてるの？」と聞かれ答えれる
When asked why I'm crying, if I can answer...
涙なんかじゃ 僕が出会えたことの意味にはまるで
...tears alone couldn't possibly do justice...
追いつかない
...to the meaning of us meeting.
この身ひとつじゃ 足りない叫び
With just this body, my cries are not enough.
君の手触れた時にだけ震えた
Only when I touched your hand did it tremble...
心があったよ
...a heart was truly there.
意味をいくつ越えれば僕らはたどり
How many meanings must we cross...
着けるのかな
...before we reach our destination?
愚かさでいい
It's fine if it's foolishness,
醜さでいい
it's fine if it's ugliness,
正しさのその先で
beyond correctness,
君と手を取りたい
I want to take your hand.
思い出せない
I cannot remember...
大切な記憶
...precious memories.
言葉にならない
They cannot be put into words,
ここにある思い
...these feelings inside my heart.
もしかしたら
If perhaps...
...if perhaps...
それだけでこの心はできてる
...that alone is what forms this heart.
もしかしたら
If perhaps...
...if perhaps...
君に気づいてと今もその胸を
...asking you to notice, even now inside that chest...
打ち鳴らす
...it keeps pounding on.
「なんで泣いてるの？」と聞かれ答えれる
When asked why I'm crying, if I can answer...
涙なんかじゃ 僕が出会えたことの意味にはまるで
...tears alone couldn't possibly do justice...
追いつかない この身ひとつじゃ
...to the meaning of us meeting.
足りない叫び
With just this body, my cries are not enough.
君の手触れた時にだけ震えた
Only when I touched your hand did it tremble...
心があったよ
...a heart was truly there.
意味をいくつ越えれば僕らはたどり
How many meanings must we cross...
着けるのかな
...before we reach our destination?
愚かさでいい
It's fine if it's foolishness,
醜さでいい
it's fine if it's ugliness,
正しさのその先で
beyond correctness,
君と生きていきたい
I want to go on living with you.
SAKURA Days (feat. AO)
[Song Title: SAKURA Days (feat. AO)]
離れていく故郷 残されるすべてが愛おしい
Leaving my hometown behind, everything left behind is dear to me.
セピアの心情 ひら開いては
Opening up my sepia-toned heart...
また思いふける
...I lose myself in thought once more.
SAKURA Days
一陣の風に
In a sudden gust of wind,
揺れた髪が懐かしい
my swaying hair feels nostalgic.
賑わいと温もりを運んでくれた
It brought me bustle and warmth.
おかげで色付いた花
Thanks to that, the flowers bloomed with color.
ある者は恋焦がれて
Some yearn deeply in love,
ある者はみんなで分かち合い
some share it with everyone,
羨望の眼差しを
...while others look on...
向けるもの
...with eyes full of envy.
舞い散る夜風に
In the night wind fluttering about,
触れれば切なく芳しい
touching it feels bittersweet and fragrant.
サヨナラとありがとうを共に送るよ
Sending both goodbye and thank you together...
おかげでまた好きになった
...thanks to that, I fell in love once more.
去るものは終えるはずなく
Those who leave cannot truly end...
来るものは拒めるわけない
And those who come cannot be turned away.
ゆえに尊い
That is why it is so precious,
桜色の日々よ
these sakura-colored days.
離れる覚悟させられる全てが愛おしい
Even being made to prepare for parting makes everything dear.
セピアの心情を開いては また
Opening up my sepia-toned feelings once again,
思い耽る
I lose myself in thought.
SAKURA Days
遥か彼方響く君の声に耳をすませば
If I listen closely to your voice echoing from far away,
少なからずその温もり思い出せるよ
I can clearly recall that warmth.
凛とした寂しさも
Even this dignified loneliness
風情と成る
becomes part of the charm.
SAKURA Days...
少なからずその温もり思い出せるよ
I can clearly recall that warmth.
麗しき
How beautiful,
SAKURA Days...
La la la...
夏じゃん！
It's summer!
見上げる空 青い海
Looking up at the sky, the blue sea!
WOW WOW
自由を描こう 僕がルール
Let me draw my freedom, I make the rules!
OH YEAH!
夏じゃん 大きくなれ 本気ボンバー！
It's summer! Growing bigger, full power Bomber!
WOW WOW
好奇心のまま GO!
Following curiosity, GO!
熱くなれ！
Get fired up!
遊びも100
100% play,
学びも100
100% learning,
時間目一杯
filling every moment to the brim!
手は抜かない ボンバー
Never slacking off, Bomber!
不順のせいや
Blaming bad luck?
絶対しないね
Never gonna do that!
そもそも人生 超一途の連続
After all, life is a series of single-minded devotions!
頼れる奴 キザなヤツ
Reliable folks, showy folks!
WOW WOW
いろいろ出会い 僕が育つ
Through various encounters, I grow!
OH YEAH!
夏じゃん 成長しろ 本気ボンバー！
It's summer! Keep growing, full power Bomber!
WOW WOW
世界みんなで Peace!
Everyone in the world, Peace!
立ち上がれ！
Stand up!
涙も出る
Tears may fall,
拍手もする
applause will follow,
褒めて褒められ
praising and being praised,
やる気も出る ボンバー
motivation ignites, Bomber!
タブー視したって
Even if made taboo,
夢はあるだろ
you still have dreams, right?
いつかは大空の彼方 本気じゃん
Someday, beyond the vast sky, going all out!
見上げる空 青い海
Looking up at the sky, the blue sea!
WOW WOW
自由を描こう 僕がルール
Let me draw my freedom, I make the rules!
OH YEAH!
夏じゃん 大きくなれ 本気ボンバー！
It's summer! Growing bigger, full power Bomber!
WOW WOW
好奇心のまま GO!
Following curiosity, GO!
熱くなれ！
Get fired up!
頼れる奴 キザなヤツ
Reliable folks, showy folks!
WOW WOW
いろいろ出会い 僕が育つ
Through various encounters, I grow!
OH YEAH!
夏じゃん 成長しろ 本気ボンバー！
It's summer! Keep growing, full power Bomber!
WOW WOW
世界みんなで Peace!
Everyone in the world, Peace!
立ち上がれ！
Stand up!
見上げる空 青い海
Looking up at the sky, the blue sea!
WOW WOW
自由を描こう 僕がルール
Let me draw my freedom, I make the rules!
JUMP!
大きくなれ
Grow bigger,
本気ボンバー!!
Serious Bomber!!
WOW WOW 好奇心のまま GO!
Wow wow, go with your curiosity, GO!
熱くなれ!
Get fired up!
HOT LIMIT
YO! SAY 夏が 胸を刺激する
YO! SAY, summer stimulates my heart,
ナマ足 魅惑の マーメイド
a captivating mermaid with bare legs.
出すとこ出して たわわになったら
Show off what you've got, and when you're luscious,
宝物の恋は やれ 爽快っ
a treasured love will feel oh-so refreshing!
ゴマカシきかない 薄着の曲線は
Unconcealable curves in light clothing,
確信犯の しなやかな STYLE!
a deliberate, supple style!
耐水性の 気持ちに切り替わる
Switching into a water-resistant mood,
瞬間(とき)の眩しさは いかがなもの
how dazzling is that moment?
ココロまで脱がされる 熱い風の誘惑に
Seduced by the hot wind that strips even your heart,
負けちゃって構わないから
it's okay to give in, so...
真夏は
midsummer is...
不祥事も キミ次第で
even scandals depend on you!
妖精たちが 夏を刺激する
Fairies stimulate the summer,
ナマ足 魅惑の マーメイド
a captivating mermaid with bare legs.
出すとこ出して たわわになったら
Show off what you've got, and when you're luscious,
宝物の恋が できそうかい?
can we fall in a treasured love?
キミじゃなくても バテ気味にもなるよ
Even if it's not you, anyone would get exhausted,
暑いヴァカンの 街は憂鬱で
in a hot vacation city, feeling gloomy.
隙を見せたら スリコミに入る
Show a weakness, and it'll slip right in,
寒いギャグなんかで 涼みたくない
I don't wanna cool down with lame jokes.
蒸せ返る熱帯夜を
Steamy tropical nights,
彩る花火のように
decorated like fireworks,
打ち上げて散る 想いなら
if those feelings shoot up and scatter...
このまま
...just like this,
抱き合って 焦がれるまで
holding each other until we burn!
妖精たちと 夏をしたくなる
I wanna spend summer with the fairies!
熱い欲望 渦巻く波間
Hot desires swirling between the waves,
出すもの出して 素直になりたい
put everything out there and be honest.
キミとボクとなら It's All Right
With you and me, it's all right!
陽射しにのびる海じゃ
In the sea stretching under the sunlight,
感じなくなってるキミを
to you who can't feel anything anymore,
日雇いの愛のくちづけで
with a kiss of temporary love,
弱らせて 焦らして 差し上げましょう
let's weaken you, tease you, and present it to you!
妖精たちが 夏を刺激する
Fairies stimulate the summer,
ナマ足 ヘソ出し マーメイド
mermaids with bare legs and bare navels.
恋に負けて お留守になる目も
Losing to love, even distracted eyes
ダイスケ的にも オールオッケー
are all okay, Daisuke-style!
妖精が夏を 誰としたくなる?
With whom do fairies want to spend summer?
ひとりでの夜に ユー・セイ・グッバイ
To lonely nights, you say goodbye!
奥の方まで 乾く間ないほど
Deep inside, with no time to dry up,
本物の恋を しませんか?
won't you fall in a real love?
Yeah!
Ina's Super Sentai!
Super Sentai?
I don't know, maybe that's our Super Sentai move.
No, no, no!
No, like this! Like this!
No, it was sexy!
Okay, sexy. Sexy Sentai, sexy Sentai.
Death-canceling Sentai.
Wait, woah, sexy, sexy, sexy!
Oh, where do we go? Okay, welcome back, everybody!
Hey, welcome back!
Hello!
What did you guys think? Having a good time?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
That's some awesome songs.
Yeah! So many good songs!
Yeah, some very close to my heart.
HOT LIMIT...
Very hot, limit of hotness!
It's already...
Too hot, you were...
Passed the... passed the hot, yeah.
Past... past the hot, yeah.
Passed the hot.
Past the hot.
Makes sense.
If you were on the stage, everything would have lit on fire.
Yeah, there's a lot of trees here, what the heck!
If we die, it will be bad.
And I did my solo, "Maji Bamba", which is a hella party song.
I had to squeeze in one more hella party song.
I hope you like it.
Some people might know it because it's like, also an anime opening.
Some people might know it because it's also like an anime opening.
Maybe some people recognize.
And you did a solo?
I did, I did "Sakura Dayz".
Because that song is a song that I did at my very first ever singing stream six years ago!
And I could not...
The pitch was like, I either sang it super low or super high!
And this time I was like, "I want to really like sing it with my whole heart!"
And so that song is really special to me, and I hope you guys enjoyed "Sakura Dayz"!
Enough of that.
That was a good reaction.
Okay, who's next? Shift the focus.
Scissors paper... Scissors paper, we need scissors paper!
That was a while.
Really beautiful.
Yeah, we look really cool together, and the stage was lovely as well.
And we went through some extra seasons, right?
We did.
We went through summer.
We're in summer right now, I don't know.
It's a little hot, so probably...
Definitely summer! It's gonna cool down from now, you guys, definitely!
Or will it get even hotter?
Yabai!
Oh crap!
Perhaps this was a sign.
Yeah.
This is, however, a PR section, isn't it?
We have to... we have to show something to you guys, right?
So, first and foremost, I'll start, I'll start. Don't all go at once, I will begin.
So first of all, as you guys know, I had my own little solo show in VR...
and at that time, I promoted to you guys this year's Mori Calliope 6th Anniversary Goods!
Yatta!
Yay!
Check 'em out, check 'em out!
Can I join in?
No, no, no, no, no!
All right, I feel left out right now, but okay, we can go on.
So if you are a fan of Mori Calliope, Dead Beats, I'm looking at you...
I have an official Happi coming out!
Official Happi!
It's really cool. I wanted to emphasize something that's like very kakkoii,
It's really cool. I wanted to emphasize something that's like very cool,
like cool darkness, and like there's an illustration of me on the back, looks like a painting.
like cool darkness, and there's an illustration of me on the back that looks like a painting.
Very illustrative... It's like half anime, very illustrative.
So I hope that you like it, it's got a skull on the front, it's awesome.
Yeah, and then Dead Beats officially get a headband!
We finally get the headband!
Get a headband, yay!
And then also, in addition to that, I have a bag...
A bag? What color is the bag?
Black, of course.
And it's got like a little window in it, you can carry...
Black bag with window.
And penlight holder!
Penlight holder, very important, and a little place where you can put your badges.
And I have four random badges that you can get...
A random one from, or you can try and buy all of them. But I hope you are very lucky!
In addition to that... so yeah, please buy the goods! Buy the goods, I say!
Now, also, my latest music video "Kei-Mei Compass"...
Should be out right now, so...
I have a brand new 3D outfit. I do lots of dancing.
I have some cool backup dancers that are real people behind me, so it's really cool.
Yeah, and it's Mori in the real world!
And I'm really big! I'm like a kaiju, also! So it's really awesome.
So please make sure you watch that. And also finally, Chad Cast has begun again!
Hurray!
Me, IRyS, and Bae, we also have a music video for our theme song too, so don't miss out on that.
That's all that I have for PR.
Oh, that's all?
Are you sure there's no more?
That's really it! I know there's a lot of stuff, sorry!
Let me go to Ina! Ina, your turn!
Well, I just revealed... or I guess last week...
revealed my new outfit!
And with that, I also released my 6th Anniversary merch!
Congratulations!
Very elegante.
Very elegant.
And of course, everyone...
Ah, the teacup!
Fancy!
A cup of tea!
Or you can put coffee in it too.
The debate continues.
And then there's a mini plushie of me in the new outfit.
Mini Ina! Yay!
And of course, I like a little bit of randomness in my life, so...
Rubber keychain...
Nice and random!
And a beautiful acrylic block.
Acrylic block! Yeah, thank you, thank you!
Y'all got... Yeah, and of course, last but not least...
Very final project, finally!
Finally! At last!
What an abyssal hymn and...
Yes, let's go! Go check it out! Very high quality, beautiful! Don't miss out.
Yes. It's releasing... to be released.
I don't know though. This is past us, it's probably out!
It's probably out! Past us doesn't know.
Likely out! Maybe at... yeah, you'll see.
Big chance it's out. If it's out, watch it. If it's not, get ready!
Get ready! That's right! Yeah!
And last but not least, yours truly, Takanashi Kiara!
This year has no anniversary merchandise, no solo, and no group, so I have nothing!
I also don't have a song coming out either, thank you! Thank you! It's okay.
There's a gift from you guys to me, and from me to me, which is I'm taking a break in October, so thank you!
Take a good rest! Take a good rest! Come back strong!
Yeah, please welcome me back when I do come back!
And yeah, please just wait for me, don't forget about me!
But you can still support me in a way by supporting all of us because we, now finally can say, we have a new song coming out!
We will perform it now, and it will come out, it will premiere after this. We will raid you into it...
...but in case the raid doesn't work, make sure to jump in there on your own. It will be on this channel.
Yeah! Yep, it will be on this channel!
Yeah, are you excited? Get hyped! Get hyped! Get hyped! They're excited, I can sense it!
It's very cool! Hold on, we're wearing this outfit that's made for us to move a lot!
Yeah! Oh yeah, bring it around town! A little preview! Ooh! Ooh!
So are you ready? I know you can do it, Ina! Ganbate! Yeah, let me do it! 1, 2, 3...
Ina! THIS IS MYTH!
Yeah! Let me go! Let's go! Let's go! Stay for the premiere, guys!
Stand up, shout it, ask the audience
Do y'all feel it?
Start up havoc, go on take a guess
Yeah, what's the name? MYTH!
Been here from the start, we laid the groundwork
Had a spark, now look it's an inferno
No, no, won't say sorry
We paved the way
Built it from zero, you get the memo?
Mythological, you're still tryina figure out
How my mind navigates where you couldn't, yeah
Try and find what we about
But know ya goin down
It's destiny, it's not a stroke of luck
Can't you see that it was meant to be
Go shout the name out
Yeah you know just what to do
If you want us say it loud
M Y T H
Hit the SOS, call the crowd in
We the best, the rest can't imagine
How pretty I'm sittin' here up at the top
Goin nonstop, show ya what we got
Make ya stressed, I bet you been sweatin'
What's our next move? We'll leave you guessin'
We don't trip up and we never stop
Had to remind ya in case you forgot
Uh huh uh huh
Now and then, we the best! So, yell it like MYTH!
Uh huh uh huh uh
I can hear 'em shout THIS IS OUR MYTH!
It ain't a surprise that we pulled up took the win
From the very start, made the biggest impression
Now we got crowds begging for us on stage
Yelling out like "MYTH!" They'd all die for me
We unstoppable, it's our reputation
You can bet on forever, we ain't done
Come try and find what we about
But know ya goin down
It's destiny, it's not a stroke of luck
Can't you see that it was meant to be
Go shout the name out
Yeah you know just what to do
If you want us say it loud
M Y T H
Hit the SOS, call the crowd in
We the best, the rest can't imagine
How pretty I'm sittin' here up at the top
Goin nonstop, show ya what we got
Make ya stressed, I bet you been sweatin'
What's our next move? We'll leave you guessin'
We don't trip up and we never stop
Had to remind ya in case you forgot
All the struggles everyday, every mistake
What we lost and gained, it's fate
We can't be shaken up, no
We'll keep going on and on and on and on
We're not afraid cause we lead the way
And when it's silent...
We can...
(Welcome to our universe)
Hit the SOS, call the crowd in
We the best, the rest can't imagine
How pretty I'm sittin' here up at the top
Goin' nonstop, show you what we got
Make ya stressed, I bet you reach sweatin'
What's our next move? We'll leave you guessin'
We don't trip up and we never stop
Had to remind ya, in case you forgot
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh
Now and then, we the best so yell it loud
MYTH!
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh
I can hear 'em go
THIS IS MYTH!
Thanks a lot, everyone! Thank you!
Bye-bye!
Stay tuned for the music video! おねがい！
Stay tuned for the music video! Please!
We're raiding you!
Yay!